{
    "id": "049339378f0e48d59812d44da690b948",
    "title": "Tense consistency exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "9eb6fa0573b74c45bdce42d2a2945ee6",
            "title": "Tense Consistency Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "If the company followed the quality guidelines, they …………………… not land in trouble.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "would",
                        "will"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The telephone …………………. while I was having a bath.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "rings",
                        "rang",
                        "is ringing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Since its conception in the early 1970s, the internet ………………… . in popularity.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "grew",
                        "grow",
                        "has grown"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "If she had acted more responsibly, everything ………………… all right.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "would be",
                        "would have been"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Thousands of people ……………………… see the art exhibition before it closes on Friday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will",
                        "would"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Captain James Cook ………………… . by Hawaiian islanders in 1779 while he was on a visit to Alaska.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "killed",
                        "had killed",
                        "was killed"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I was terribly disappointed with my marks because I …………………… really hard.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "worked",
                        "had worked"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The teacher started asking questions as soon as she ……………………… the lessons.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "finished",
                        "has finished",
                        "was finished"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Everyone …………………… that she would return safely.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "hoped",
                        "had hoped",
                        "has hoped"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The boy confessed that he ………………… . the money.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has taken",
                        "had taken"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}